The world lived a normal life, filled with safety and peace.
كان العالم يعيش حياة طبيعية يسودها الأمن والسلام
People enjoyed safety, and children played in harmony.
حيث كان الناس ينعمون بالأمن، والأطفال يلعبون في وئام
In the labs, scientists worked hard to serve humanity.
وفي المختبرات، كان العلماء يعملون بجد لخدمة البشرية
Suddenly the ground shook, and a terrifying danger appeared.
وفجأة اهتزت الأرض تحت الأقدام وظهر خطر مرعب
A global invasion began; giant creatures seized our cities.
بدأ غزو عالمي واحتلت الكائنات العملاقة مدننا
These creatures took over the world's landmarks; nowhere was spared.
احتلت هذه المخلوقات معالم العالم ولم ينجُ منها مكان
Panic spread everywhere and emergency warnings were issued.
ساد الذعر في كل مكان وأُطلقت تحذيرات طارئة
Epidemics spread and hospitals filled with the sick and weary.
انتشرت الأوبئة وامتلأت المشافي بالمصابين والتعب
These organisms caused severe skin diseases and painful scars.
تسببت هذه الكائنات في أمراض جلدية خطيرة وندب مؤلمة
The world's scientists gathered at the research center to face the threat.
اجتمع علماء العالم في مركز الأبحاث لمواجهة التهديد
Not alien monsters — but protists that had gone out of control.
ليست وحوشاً فضائية بل طلائعيات خرجت عن السيطرة
A specialized science team was formed to protect humanity.
تم تشكيل فريق علمي متخصص لحماية البشرية
Sadeem — strategic analysis expert
سديم — خبير التحليل الاستراتيجي
Atheer — molecular analysis specialist
أثير — متخصصة التحليل الجزيئي
Nouray — the team's scientific leader
نوراي — القائدة العلمية لهذا الفريق
Kayser — field defense expert
كايسر — خبير الدفاع الميداني
The mission began — Sadeem defeats the pathogenic Giardia.
بدأ الفريق المهمة، سديم يقضي على جيارديا الممرضة
And Atheer defeats Trichomonas with brilliant scientific skill.
وأثير تهزم التريكوموناس ببراعة علمية فائقة
Nouray rescues civilians while analyzing the dangerous samples.
نوراي تنقذ المدنيين بينما تحلل العينات الخطيرة
And Kayser eliminates Leishmania with advanced techniques.
وكايسر يقضي على الليشمانيا بتقنيات متطورة
Stop! This Paramecium is one of the beneficial protists.
توقفوا! هذا البراميسيوم من الطلائعيات النافعة
Not all protists are harmful — they must be protected.
ليست جميع الطلائعيات ضارة ويجب الحفاظ عليها
This is only the beginning... help us bring safety back again!
نحن في البداية... فساعدونا ليعمّ الأمان مرة أخرى